imtalk.org 2019-06-24

# IMTalk.org - Privacy Policy

IMTalk.org Privacy Policy

IMTalk.org, has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to user privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for IMTalk.org, as well as e-mail newsletters. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected on IMTalk.org and not to information that is collected by IMTalk.org through any other means. Your visit to IMTalk.org is subject to this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Personal Information Collection and Use**

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you submit an inquiry to us, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact details (name, e-mail address, etc.).

When you submit your personally identifiable information through IMTalk.org, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will use the information you provide us only for the purpose of responding to your inquiry or in connection with the service for which you provided such information. We may also use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans.

In addition, we may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal proceeding or governmental request.

**2\. E-mail addresses**

We do not want you to receive unwanted e-mail from us. We try to make it easy to opt-out of any service you have asked to receive. If you sign-up to our e-mail newsletters we do not sell, exchange or give your e-mail address to a third party.

E-mail addresses are collected via the IMTalk.org Users have to physically opt-in to receive the IMTalk.org newsletter and a verification e-mail is sent. IMTalk.org is clearly and conspicuously named at the point of collection.

IMTalk.org uses e-mail addresses to send its weekly newsletters and occasional mailings to assist in market research.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by e-mailing us at admin@imtalk.org.

The security of your personal information, including your e-mail address is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during registration and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure, however. Therefore, though we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about the security on our Web site, please visit our "[Contact Us](http://www.imtalk.org/sendmessage.php)" page and a designated IMTalk.org correspondent will respond to your query.

If we decide to change our e-mail practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we think appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to our e-mail practices, we will notify you here, by e-mail, and by means of a notice on our home page.

**3\. Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your e-mail address changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate your details by visiting the [Contact Us](http://www.imtalk.org/sendmessage.php) page.

**4\. Tracking Technologies**

Tracking technologies are set up via the IMTalk.org newsletter to monitor open and click performance. Cookies are only used once a user enters the IMTalk.org Web site in order to identify, discriminate and count the unique users visiting our Web site.

**5\. Log Files**

IMTalk.org records details of individual accesses to its Web pages. This information may include details of Internet IP addresses and browser types. We use this information to provide a more relevant site for you. In addition, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Access by third parties to full log files may be allowed under controlled circumstances for the purposes of auditing. Abstracted log information not showing individual's actual Internet addresses is provided to third parties.

**6\. Cookies**

IMTalk.org uses cookies to improve user experience, such as enhancing navigation and relevancy of product and information on the site. Your Web browser should allow you to choose whether or not to allow cookies - you can still use our site if you have them disabled. For more information on cookies, you can visit www.cookiecentral.com.

**7\. Third Party Sites**

IMTalk.org does not sell products or services, but directs you to third party Web sites that do. These sites may collect personally identifiable information from you, such as your name, address, credit card details or details pertaining to other methods of payment. These sites may have their own privacy policies which will govern how such sites use and share your personally identifiable information. In addition, IMTalk.org displays third party booking tools. When you utilize these third party booking tools, you are subject to the terms, conditions and privacy policies of those third parties.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on IMTalk.org. Please note that IMTalk.org has no input into, and is not responsible for, the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other Web sites you link to from IMTalk.org.

**8\. Third Party Advertisers**

The advertising banners and other forms of advertising appearing on this Web site are sometimes delivered to you, on our behalf, by a third party. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, the third party may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. For more information on cookies, you can visit www.cookiecentral.com.

**9\. Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell certain aspects of our entities or assets. In such transactions, user information, including personally identifiable information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your personal information on IMTalk.org you agree that your data may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances.

**10\. Notification of Changes**

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Please note that our rights to use your personally identifiable information will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used.

**11\. Electronic Privacy Policy (P3P)**

In addition to this standard Privacy Policy, IMTalk.org uses an electronic privacy policy (P3P) that can be automatically retrieved and interpreted by certain web browsers. Our P3P policy states that it is valid for 52 weeks from the time it is loaded by a user.

**12\. Comments**

We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to IMTalk.org is an excellent one and that your privacy is respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us by e-mail via our Feedback link:

**13\. Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.   

**14\. Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 2010/12/10
